thewatchgallery.com 2018-02-05

# Privacy Policy

### Introduction

As keen users of other internet sites, we fully appreciate the importance of privacy on the internet. In common with all shopping websites, we collect personal data when you shop or interact with www.thewatchgallery.com. We use this information to make your experience of our site as enjoyable as possible. We use it to process your orders, advise you of any problems or delays and to occasionally, when we have your consent, send you new product alerts, offers and promotions. Our website may also use a website recording service which may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, page scrolling and any text keyed into website forms. Data collected by this service is used to improve our website usability. The information collected is stored and is used for aggregated and statistical reporting, and is not shared with anybody else.

We collect information for the following purposes:

  * To deliver orders placed by you
  * To verify your payment details and prevent fraudulent transactions
  * To obtain card authorisation and process payments
  * To contact you in the event of a problem with your order
  * Where your consent has been given, to contact you with alerts, offers and promotions

We use the very latest 128bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to ensure that your payment information is safely encrypted, making it virtually impossible for unauthorised access to your details. We work with the very best security partners in the business – our SSL certificate is supplied by Verisign, and SagePay process our secure payments – both companies are world leaders in their fields.

### Data Protection

We are a registered data user under the Data Protection Act. We will never pass your details on to a third party for marketing purposes. These are the circumstances in which we will share your data:

  * With the payment service we use to authorise and process your payments – in such instances, we provide them only with the data they require to perform these services.
  * In certain cases we may use an additional fraud screening service to ensure the legitimate use of your payment details.
  * In the unlikely event that our business assets are ever purchased by another company.

If you have any questions about your personal data or our privacy policy contact us at [help@thewatchgallery.com](mailto:help@thewatchgallery.com) or write to: The Data Protection Officer - The Watch Gallery Ltd. 16 Dufour's Place. London. W1F 7SP

### Your Contact Preferences

If you have registered or purchased from us, we may ask for email and telephone contact details in order to undertake any services you may have requested from us – namely: registration for offers; participation in competitions, or purchase of goods.

You can change your contact preferences by logging into the My Account section of the site and updating your Newsletter Subscriptions.

### Third Party Links

This site may contain links to and from websites maintained by third parties. If you follow a link to any of these sites, please note that they have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies – please check the relevant privacy information on such sites before submitting personal data.

### Security

We work with the best online security partners to ensure that your payment details are safely encrypted and protected using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. This means you cannot inadvertently send private information through an unsecure connection. When sending private data look out for the padlock sign at the foot of your browser – the root of our URL will also change from HTTP to HTTPS.

In addition to encrypting your information and using the latest SSL technology, we also provide an additional layer of payment card security, established by the world’s leading payment system providers to protect consumers from unauthorised payments:

### Verified by Visa

Verified by Visa provides an additional password-protected level of security when using your Visa card for online purchases. You can sign up for Verified by Visa next time you place an order with us or alternatively, contact your payment card provider directly to set up the service. Once signed up, your internet purchases on 1000’s of websites will be protected by an additional level of authentication. When using Verified by Visa you’ll be asked to enter a password, known only to yourself, in addition to the normal payment card details asked for when making a purchase.

### MasterCard SecureCode

MasterCard SecureCode is a service that password-protects your MasterCard /Maestro payment card details, giving you added security when shopping online. The service allows you to create a password that is known only to yourself, to use every time you use your card online.

To register for MasterCard SecureCode all you need to do is follow the instructions next time you place an order with us. Alternatively, you can sign up by contacting the bank that issued your Mastercard/Maestro card directly. You will be asked to create a password (also known as a SecureCode) for your payment card. You only need to do this once then whenever you use the card online you will be asked to enter the password when you check out. If you have already registered, you will be prompted to enter your SecureCode when you order. To find out more information about these services visit the [MasterCard SecureCode website](http://www.mastercard.com/uk/personal/en/cardholderservices/securecode/index.html).
